## NGUYEN TRAN PHUONG DUY

#### Fullstack Developer

**└** (+84) 966 740 812 | ✓ duyntp2000@gmail.com | **♀** howznguyen | ₩ howznguyen

#### **i** INTRODUCE

With many years of experience in web programming and has programmed many projects. I want to use these skills to contribute to the company and develop myself. I am a person who is always willing to learn new things and always try to do my best.

### **EDUCATION**

■ [2018-2022] Ho Chi Minh CityUniversity of Food Industry■ [2015-2018] Phan Dinh PhungHigh School

#### **©** CAREER OBJECTIVE

- Enhance my knowledge and capabilities by working in a dynamic environment.
- Devote to knowledge and strength to the company.
- Become a key and important member of the company during working time.

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Responsibility
- Self-learning
- Teamwork
- Flexibility
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Inventive
- Decisive
- Presentation

### **EXPERIENCE**

- iii [12/2016 05/2022] ITRUM Forum Founder
- Founded a forum for IT students to share knowledge and experience.
- Managed and developed the forum.
- iii [04/2020 Present] MindX Technology School Programming

#### Lecturer

- Assisted in the instruction of lecture for web and game development
- Instruct and guide students in using Scratch, GameMaker, HTML,CSS,

JS, Firebase, Python

- Used to be responsible for managing and coordinating lecturers for the company.
- iii [07/2021 01/2023] Cube System Vietnam Co., Ltd Web

#### Developer

- Develop and maintain company projects.
- Design and implement the database of the company's projects.
- Using PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, ExpressJS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap to develop system.

### </> </> <//> SKILLS

😈 😈 HTML & CSS

65%

📠 📵 JavaScript & NodeJS

70%

👜 👺 PHP & Laravel

85%

70%

🗬 Python

**⇒** Docker

\_\_\_\_\_

🔥 Linux

70%

65%

# NGUYỄN TRẦN PHƯƠNG DUY

#### Fullstack Developer

**L** (+84) 966 740 812 | ✓ duyntp2000@gmail.com | **G** howznguyen | ✓ howznguyen

### 3 GIỚI THIỀU

Với kinh nghiệm lập trình Website nhiều năm và đã làm nhiều dự án khác nhau. Tôi muốn sử dụng kỹ năng và kiến thức của mình để đóng góp cho công ty cũng như phát triển bản thân. Tôi cũng là một người luôn sẵn sàng học hỏi những điều mới và luôn cố gắng làm hết sức mình.

### ₽ Học Vấn

■ [2018-2022] Đại Học Công Nghiệp Thực Phẩm TP.HCM■ [2015-2018] THPT Phan Đình Phùng

### **Ø** MỤC TIÊU

- Mong muốn được làm việc trong môi trường chuyên nghiệp, năng động, nhiều cơ hội phát triển bản thân.
- Cống hiến hết mình để đạt được mục tiêu của công ty.
- Trở thành một thành viên chủ chốt và quan trọng của công ty trong thời gian làm việc.

### 🖶 KỸ NĂNG MỀM

- 🗸 Tinh thân trách nhiệm
- 🕜 Tự học hỏi
- Làm viêc nhóm
- Linh hoat
- 🕜 Giải quyết vấn đề
- Giao tiếp
- Sáng tạo
- 🕜 Ra quyết định
- 🕜 Thuyết trình

### 🖶 KINH NGHIỆM

- 🗰 [2016 2022] ITRUM Forum Sáng Lập
- Thành lập diễn đàn để sinh viên CNTT chia sẻ kiến thức và kinh nghiệm
- Quản lý và phát triển diễn đàn
- iii [2020 Hiện tại] MindX Technology School Giảng Viên Lập Trình
- Hỗ trợ và hướng dẫn học viên trong việc phát triển Web và Game
- Hướng dẫn học sinh sử dụng Scratch, GameMaker, HTML,CSS, JS, Firebase, Python
- Đã từng chịu trách nhiệm quản lý, điều phối giảng viên cho công ty.
- 🗰 [2021 2023] Cube System Vietnam Co., Ltd Web Developer
- Phát triển và duy trì các dự án của công ty.
- Thiết kế và triển khai các cơ sở dữ liệu của các dự án của công ty.
- Sử dụng PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, ExpressJS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap trong việc phát triển hệ thống.

### </> </> </> </> KŸ NĂNG CHÍNH

**፱ ፱** HTML & CSS

65%

ந 📵 JavaScript & NodeJS

70%

🕮 👺 PHP & Laravel

85%

🗬 Python

70%

🐡 Docker

👃 Linux

70%

65%